-埃文  谢谢你载我回家  -小意思
-Thanks for the ride home, Evan. -Sure.
你看我练习不觉得很无聊吗
You didn't mind sitting through my practice?
噢  不不不  一点也不无聊
Oh, no no no, not at all.
你穿队服时好帅啊
You look cute in your uniform.
-我在游泳队  -是啊
-I'm on the swim team. -Yeah.
-嘿  -噢  埃文  这是我老弟  盖比
-Hey. -Oh, uh, Evan, this is my brother Gabe.
-盖比  这位是埃文  -等一下
-Gabe, this is Evan. - Wait a minute.
-我看你好眼熟啊  -你肯定看走眼了
-Don't I know you from somewhere? -I don't think so.
我以前绝对见过你
I've definitely seen you before.
嘿  不如检查下你的房间
Hey, why don't you go check your room?
一定会发现不少线索的
Lots of really good clues there.
-我该走了  明天见  -拜
-I should get going. See you tomorrow? -Bye.
拜
Yeah.
亲娘啊  我谢你
Oh god. Thanks a lot.
我又怎么了
What did I do?
过去的两周里  他每天都载我回家
He's been driving me home every day for the past two weeks.
本以为今天会是我们的初次约会
I think he was finally going to ask me out
谁又想到你那诡异的言语以及行为
Until you scared him off with all your talking
把他给吓跑了...
And pointing and...
抱歉了  但他看起来真的很眼熟
I'm sorry, but he looks familiar.
难道是我以前的夏令营辅导员
Was he my camp counselor?
不是不是  他看起来好像怕我
No no no, he seemed afraid of me,
但又不是那种害怕
But not that afraid of me.
像埃文这么帅的小伙怎么会认识你呢
Why would a totally hot guy like Evan know you?
我知道了  斯莱格沃特
What's wrong with me? Slegowart!
你说话就像“斯莱格沃特”
You say things like "slegowart."
不不  斯莱格沃特是口袋游戏王中的角色
No no, slegowart is a character in pokeo.
（注：口袋游戏王为口袋妖怪与游戏王的综合体）
这就是为什么我认识埃文了  在游戏店
That's how I know evan-- from the game store.
埃文玩口袋游戏王
Evan plays pokeo?
那些有白痴卡通生物的脑残纸牌游戏
That nerdy card game with those stupid cartoon creatures?
不是
No.
埃文玩的口袋游戏王  乃超酷纸牌游戏
Evan plays pokeo, the fantasy card game
该纸牌游戏需要具备高超的技术和出色的战略
That requires a keen level of skill and strategy.
但埃文为什么要玩那玩意  那都是小孩玩的
But why would Evan play that? That's for little kids.
数码宝贝才是给小孩玩的
Wigimon is for little kids.
口袋游戏王是给九岁及九岁以上儿童玩的
Pokeo is for nine and up.
坑爹呐
How is that possible?
如今大帅哥变成呆子了
Now the cute hot guy is a secret nerd?
其实  这世上的许多纸牌游戏
Well, many of us in the world of fantasy card games
还是很引人入胜的
Are considered quite attractive.
生活搞得一团糟
<i>Today's all burnt toast </i>
就要迟到  爸爸在叫
<i>Running late, and dad jokes</i>
■
本字幕由★迪幻字幕组★为您奉献
欢迎登录 www.Deefun.com
我左脚的鞋子有没有人看到
<i>Has anybody seen my left shoe</i>
我闭上眼  咬口早餐
<i>I close my eyes, take a bite</i>
跳上车子  放声大笑
<i>Grab a ride, laugh out loud</i>
■
翻译： Johnny-Z  coala1234
哎呀  老爸  鞋子就在房顶上
<i>There it is up on the roof</i>
我也曾这样生活  我已经顺利走过
<i>I've been there, I've survived</i>
■
校订： line
所以听取我的建议
<i>So just take my advice</i>
宝贝  不要放弃
<i>Hang in there, baby</i>
■
后期： Johnny-Z
世界有很多疯狂无奈
<i>Things are crazy</i>
可是我知道你会有美好将来
<i>But I know your future's bright</i>
宝贝  不要放弃
<i>Hang in there, baby</i>
不要怀疑
<i>There's no maybe</i>
一切终会如你所愿
<i>Everything turns out all right</i>
生活有悲有喜
<i>Your life is up and down</i>
但是请相信我  坚持就有好结果
<i>But trust me it comes back around</i>
你会喜欢将来的你
<i>You're gonna love</i> <i>who you turn out to be</i>
宝贝  不要放弃
<i>Hang in there, baby.</i>
查莉成长日记  第二季第六集
Good Luck Charlie  S02E06  A L.A.R.P. in the Park
-老妈回来了  -嘿  亲爱的
-Mom's home! -Hey, honey!
嘿  今晚有宴会  你给我租到晚礼服了吗
Hey, the banquet's tonight. Did you rent me a tux?
-就在那  -太好了
-It's right over there. -Okay.
是那种让我看起来像是詹姆斯·邦德的礼服吗
Did you get me the one that makes me look like james bond?
是的  亲爱的  我给你租了魔幻礼服
Yeah, honey, I got you the magic tux.
妈  你给我打印报告了吗
Mom, did you type my report?
你知道我手指受伤了
You know, because of my broken finger?
-是的  我打印好了  -报告是讲什么的
-Yes, I typed your report. -What's it about?
-内战  -我还应该了解什么
-The civil war. -What's my take?
-你干嘛不自己看  -算了  那是老师的工作
-Why don't you read it? -No, that's the teacher's job.
妈  我饿了  有啥能吃的吗
Mom, I'm hungry. Is there anything to eat?
你看你旁边有什么能喂饱你的吗
What's that thing filled with food right next to you?
老爸吗
Dad?
嘿  老妈  周六早上能帮我
Hey, mom, could you help out
去下学校组织的洗车活动吗
With my school car wash on Saturday morning?
宝贝  那是我唯一的休息日
Honey, that's my only day off work.
太好了  看来你有时间了
Perfect. So you're free.
好了  带上你自己的擦布
All right, bring your own chamois.
好了  好了  打住
Okay okay, stop.
请给我五分钟的安宁
I need five minutes of peace, please.
说得太好了  你尽管坐在那里放松好了
That is a wonderful idea. You just sit there and relax.
谢了
Thank you.
-我怎么没看见领结  -天啊  好了  查莉咱俩走
-I'm not seeing the bow tie-- -oh my-- okay, come on. Let's go, charlie.
你现在是唯一不招我烦的了
You're the only one who isn't annoying me right now.
怎么没有封面啊
There's no cover page.
我的鼻子在哪
Where's my nose?
猜对了  太好了
That's my nose. That's great.
看看你还有什么本事  我的耳朵在哪
What else do you know? Where's my ear?
又对了
That's my ear.
我的眼睛呢
Where's my eye?
嗷  疼啊  老天啊
Ow!  Ow. Oh my gosh.
-哇噢  被她整了  疼啊  -怎么了
-Wow, she got me.  Ow. -What?
嗷  查莉捅到我的眼睛了
Ow, Charlie poked me in the eye.
噢  我睁不开眼睛了  鲍伯  疼死了
Oh, I can't open my eye. Bob, it really hurts.
老妈  也许你应该去医院检查下
Mom, maybe you should get it checked out.
泰迪  我可是个护士
Teddy, I'm a nurse.
我不需要你告诉我
I don't need you to tell me
什么时候去检查
When I need to get something checked out.
鲍伯  我需要检查下
Bob, I need to get this checked out.
好了  艾米  看来你的眼角膜并无大碍
Well, Amy, it doesn't look like your cornea is scratched.
我给你开点眼药水
I'm going to prescribe some drops.
你需要整晚都戴这个眼罩  祝你早日康复
Wear this eyepatch overnight and you'll be good to go.
你说康复  在家里康复吗
You mean go, as in go home?
难道这不好吗
Well, that's good news, isn't it?
那个  回家就代表着烧饭  打扫
Well, home is where the cooking and cleaning
洗衣  家庭作业  老公和孩子们
And laundry and homework and husband and kids and--
我可不想回家
I don't wanna go home.
但你又没病
But there's nothing wrong with you.
我是说你的眼睛
Well, with your eye.
我就不能留院观察一宿吗
Can't you just keep me overnight for observation?
艾米  身为护士  你应该知道这并不合适
Amy, as a nurse you know that's not appropriate.
这里又不是旅馆
This is not a hotel.
你知道还有什么不合适的吗  迈耶斯医生
You know what else isn't appropriate, dr. Meyers?
告诉人们你在免费诊所上班期间
Telling people you're working at the free clinic
却在丹佛乡村俱乐部
When you're really playing 18 holes
打高尔夫球
At the denver country club.
我觉着207房挺适合你
I think you'll enjoy room 207.
老妈去哪了
Where's mom?
噢不  她的那什么是不是没有了
Oh no, she didn't make it, did she?
你妈没事了
Your mom is going to be fine.
不是  我在说烘肉卷
No, I'm talking about the meatloaf.
她是不是根本没做烘肉卷
She didn't make it, did she?
看来  你对这位赐予你生命的女人
You know, the concern you have for the woman
的关心还真是惊天地  泣鬼神啊
Who gave birth to you is overwhelming.
她打算把它裹在培根里
She was going to wrap it in bacon.
真的
Really?
等一下  我瞎想什么呢
Wait a minute. What am I thinking about?
我今晚有宴会的
I've got my banquet tonight.
嘿  你想来吗
Hey, you wanna come with?
丹佛害虫控制协会将上演一出好戏
Denver pest control association puts on quite a do.
-没想好呢  -何乐而不为呢
-I don't know. -Why not?
因为听完那句话还能保持清醒对我来说还真不容易
Because I had trouble staying awake during that sentence.
是说你不想看到你老爸我
Are you telling me you don't wanna see your old man
赢得年度最佳灭虫者奖吗
Win the exterminator of the year award?
好了  你觉着你每年都会赢得那个奖项
Oh right, that award you think you're going to win every year,
但是从没实现过  因为默里总是蝉联该奖项
But you don't because Murray always does.
听着  不可能某人可以
Look, there is no way that the same guy
-一直蝉联该奖项  -为什么不成
-Can win every year. -Why not?
某人和该奖项就是一直无缘啊
The same guy loses every year.
算了  告诉你吧  默里什么的就别谈了
All right, you know what? Enough about murray.
你就不想看到你的父亲上台领奖吗
Do you wanna see your father win the award or not?
难道默里是我的父亲
Murray's my dad?
老妈
Mom?
天啊
Oh my--
感觉好点了吗
How are you feeling?
-噢  好点了  -是吗
-Oh, a little better. -Yeah?
但是我好想念你还有查莉还有...
But I miss you and charlie and...
其他人
The others.
很高兴我不是其他人里面的
I'm glad one of us is doing well.
很好
That's nice.
感谢前来探望
Thank you for coming.
老妈  我刚来啊
Mom, I just got here.
也是  哈  好吧  你怎么样了
Oh right.  Ha. Well, how are you?
这个嘛  我看上了个男生
Well, actually there's this boy Evan
叫埃文  但是...
That I really like, but, um...
他的有些事让我很是郁闷
I found out something kind of disturbing about him.
他爱玩口袋游戏王
He's into pokeo.
口袋游戏王  就是盖比爱玩的那个
Pokeo?  That thing Gabe likes?
宝贝  你看上他哪点了
Well, honey, what would you see in a guy like that?
看  这是埃文游泳比赛时候的照片
Well, this is Evan at a swim meet.
好呀  这倒解释了很多疑问
Yeah, that explains that.
宝贝  人无完人  每个人都有瑕疵
Well, honey, no one's perfect. Everyone has their flaws.
你觉着当我发现你爸是灭虫的后很兴奋吗
You think I was thrilled when I found out your father was into bugs?
但你熬过去了吗
But you got over it?
是的  那就是我所做的  熬过去
Yeah, that's what I did-- got over it.
听着  宝贝  恋爱意味着宽容对方
Look, honey, relationships are about compromise.
如果你真心喜欢他
If you really like this guy,
你就要爱屋及乌
Try being interested in things he's interested in.
在我和你爸第二次约会的时候
On my second date with your father
我对他侃侃而谈了三个有关树皮甲虫的知识
I threw out three facts about bark beetles.
哈哈  他就被我降服了
Ha ha, the man was mine.
好了  我已经占用你足够多的时间了
Well, I've taken up enough of your time.
老妈  你不是另外的那只眼睛受伤了吗
Mom, didn't you get poked in the other eye?
不不不  就是这只眼睛
No no, it was-- it was this eye.
我很确定是另外那只
I'm pretty sure it was the other one.
不是  不是
No no no no.
噢天啊  宝贝  让老娘我休息休息
Oh gosh, let mama rest, dear.
让老娘我休息休息
Let mama rest.
好了  咱们再来一遍
Okay, let's do this one more time.
如果我出快龙卡
I'm putting down my dragony card.
你该出什么卡
What's your counterattack?
呃...
Um...
-独角虫卡  -独角虫卡
-Weepok? -Weepok?
你有沙拉曼斯卡不出  却出独角虫卡
You played a weepok when you could have played a scalamaster?
沙拉曼斯  就是那个长着吸盘的
Scalamaster-- that's-- that's the octopus dude
章鱼哥吗
With the suction cup thingies?
漩涡  那东西叫漩涡
Vortexes. They're called vortexes.
告诉你吧  我不和你玩了
You know what? I can't work with you.
你对神话世界没有一点敬意
You have no respect for the mythical world of dort.
噢不要
Oh no.
盖比  请再给我一次机会吧
Gabe, please, just give me one more chance.
算了吧  算了
Forget it. Forget it.
-无药可救了  -说的没错
-This is hopeless. -You're right.
我感觉就像加西欧对抗密斯罗德
I feel like Gasio going up against Misrod.
等下  你说对了
Wait a minute. That wasn't wrong.
-没说错吗  -没有没有
-It wasn't? -No no.
加西欧无力对抗密斯罗德  因为
Gasio would have no chance against misrod because?
因为火系克草系
Because grass power is no match for volcano power?
没错  没错
Yes yes yes!
哇噢  老师真的可以改变你
Wow, teachers really do make a difference.
亲爱的
Honey?
亲爱的  嘿
Honey?  Hey.
感觉怎么样了  亲爱的
How are you feeling, sweetie?
好多了
I've been better.
我给你带来了一些可以让你振作起来的东西
Well, I got something that's going to help cheer you up.
看
Tada!
年度最佳灭虫者
Exterminator of the year!
你赢了  太不可思议了
You won? That is fantastic!
噢  亲爱的  我太为你骄傲了
Oh, honey, I'm so proud of you!
我的获奖感言无与伦比
I gave a great big speech and everything.
-噢  你在台上表扬我了吗  -当然了
-Aw, did you say something nice about me? -Of course I did.
PJ  他用手机录下了全过程
P.J., he got the whole thing recorded on his phone.
-快拿给你妈看看  -是啊  快让我看看
-Show her the speech. -Yeah, let me see it.
爸爸  我可以和你去外面说说话吗
Dad, can I speak to you outside for a second?
-什么  -好吧
- What? - Yeah.
-你到底在做什么  -走走走
- What the heck are you doing? - Go go go.
-你不能让妈妈看那段视频  -为什么不
- You can't show mom that video. - Why not?
-因为你没有感谢她  -太好笑了
- Because you don't thank her. - Oh, that's ridiculous.
-你甚至都没有提到她  -我当然提到了
- You don't even mention her. - Of course I did.
让我们看一看
Let's take a look.
好吧  我该从哪儿开始
Okay.  Oh, man, where do I start?
哦也  当着你的面  默里
Oh yeah, in your face, Murray!
啊
Huh?
我想
<i>I want to--</i>
你知道什么  我想
You know what? I want to--
我想谢谢我的孩子PJ  泰迪  盖比  查莉
I want to thank my kids p.J., teddy, gabe, charlie,
他们是让我每天努力工作的动力
Who make me want to work so hard every day.
赞美下那边的虫子怎么样
Oh, and how about a shout-out to all the bugs out there, huh?
因为没有它们我们就不会在这里了
Without whom none of us would be here.
最重要的是我想谢谢
Most importantly I want to thank
今晚一位非常特别的女士
One very special lady tonight--
我的女助手  艾瑞斯
My waitress! Iris!
继续努力  宝贝
Keep 'em comin', baby!
我是大赢家
I'm a winner!
哦  大事不好
Wow, that's not good.
老天爷啊
Oh man.
我该怎么办
What am I gonna do?
-你可以告诉妈妈真相  -或者
- You could tell mom the truth. - Or?
我可以告诉妈妈真相
I could tell mom the truth?
或者
Or?
我们可以偷偷从这儿溜出去  一会儿再想这些
We could sneak out of here and think of something later?
叮叮叮叮
Ding ding ding ding.
再次感谢你送我回来
Thanks again for giving me a ride.
再次感谢你一直等到我的游泳训练结束
Thanks again for waiting till my swim practice was over.
谢我什么  谢谢你自己吧
Thank me? Thank <i>you.</i>
-明天还是这时候  -听起来不错
- Same time tomorrow? - Yeah, sounds good.
-好吧  -你能帮我个忙吗
- All right. - Hey, could you do me a favor
帮我把钥匙从我的背包里拿出来
And grab my keys out of my backpack?
好的
Sure.
你有口袋游戏王牌
You have pokeo cards?
不  你不能看这些
Oh no, you weren't supposed to see those.
真不好意思
I'm so embarrassed.
没什么  我也在玩口袋游戏王
Don't be. I'm into pokeo too.
等等  什么
Wait, what?
我不想提及此事  因为
I didn't want to say anything because...
我怕你会认为我很奇怪
I was afraid you'd think I was weird.
等等  那也正是我不想提及此事的原因
Wait, yeah, that's why I didn't want to say anything to you.
我的梦想是成为一个四级纸牌大师
My dream is to become a level-four card master
赢得我的蛇发女怪盾牌
And earn my gorgonic shield.
那也是我的梦想
That's my dream.
等等  什么
Wait, what?
你可以和我一起出去吗
Will you go out with me?
沙拉曼斯卡有涡旋吗
Does scalamaster have vortexes?
有的
Yeah.
你确定这有用吗
Are you sure this is going to work?
相信我  它看着会很像你真正的获奖感言的
Trust me, it's going to look exactly like your real acceptance speech.
但你也许想把查莉移走
But you might want to move charlie.
啊  好的
Huh?  Oh okay.
到这儿来  亲爱的  过来
Come here, sweetie. Come on.
我们帮爸爸骗骗妈妈
Let's help daddy deceive mommy.
让我们变些戏法  鲍比
Okay let's make some magic, bobby.
-准备好了  -是的
- Ready? - Yeah.
-是的
- Okay. - Okay.
开始
On.  Action!
嘿嘿嘿
Hey hey! Hey, okay, whoo.
我有  不不不
I have-- no. No no no.
我想
I want to--
我想谢谢我的妻子艾米·邓肯
I want to thank my wife amy b. Duncan.
停  爸爸  你就像块木头一样僵硬
Cut.  Dad, you are stiff as a board.
-帮帮我  -来点感情
- Help me. - Show me some emotion.
好的  准备好  开始
Okay. All right, action.
非常感谢颁这个奖给我
Thank you for this award.
这是我生命中最重要的时刻之一
This is one of the great moments of my life.
停  我要接一下电话
Cut.  I gotta take this.
你好
Hello?
没有  我现在一点也不忙
Oh no, I'm not doing anything.
怎么了
What's going on?
抱歉  我们的初次约会我得把查莉带去
Sorry I had to bring charlie on our first date.
我还以为我妈妈现在已经从医院回来了
I kind of thought my mom would be out of the hospital by now.
其实我很高兴你带她来
Actually I'm excited you brought her.
她会让约会变得更美好
She's going to make this even better.
是啊  这什么意思  我们在做什么
Yeah, what is this anyway? What are we doing?
-我们玩Larp  -Larp
- We're going to larp. - Larp?
“larp”就是真人角色扮演
"larp" stands for "live action role-play."
任何人都可以用纸牌玩口袋游戏王
Anyone can play pokeo with cards,
但是当你玩起角色扮演时
But when you put on the costumes and you act it out,
就把它带到了一个全新的水平
It takes it to a whole new level.
你在开玩笑吧
Oh, you're joking, right?
噢  你不是在开玩笑
Oh, you're not joking.
伙计们  这是泰迪和查莉
Guys, this is teddy and charlie.
泰迪查莉  这是斯莱格玛
Teddy and Charlie, this is Slugmar,
独角虫  沙拉曼斯卡还有古拉贡
Weepok, Scalamaster, and Gulagon.
你居然带了个女孩  我们从来没有过女孩
You brought girls. We've never had girls.
好的
Okay.
既然我们没有穿
Well, since we're not really dressed
真人角色扮演的衣服
For the whole larping thing,
你们玩的时候  查莉和我会坐在那边
Charlie and I are just going to go sit over here while you guys play.
不不不  别着急  我都想好了
Oh, no no no, don't worry. I thought of everything.
最给力的是我们在公开场合
And the best part is we're out in public.
噢  坏消息  妈妈
Oh, bad news, mom.
我的内战报告得了个B
You got a b- on my civil war report.
这不是你的最佳水平
Not your best work.
下回我会更努力的
I'll try harder next time.
所以  亲爱的  准备好看我的演讲了吗
So, honey, ready to see my big speech?
我用我的电话拍的
That I shot with my phone...
在饭店...
At the hotel...
那天晚上
The other night.
快点播放吧
Just hit "play."
谢谢  谢谢  谢谢
<i>thank you, thank you,</i> <i>thank you.</i>
谢谢  丹佛害虫控制协会
Thank you, denver pest control association.
今年的饭店不是很好
Not a very nice hotel this year.
呃  预算缩减
Uh, it's budget cuts.
你知道  赢得一个像这样的奖项很不可思议
You know, winning an award like this is incredible,
但是我却成为了获奖者
But I'm already a winner
因为我出色的妻子艾米
Because of my wonderful wife amy.
当我想起这为伟大的女人...
When I think about this amazing woman...
我很激动
I get all emotional.
等等  那是什么
Wait, what is that?
PJ  倒回去
P.J., rewind.
这里  停
There, pause.
-鲍伯  怎么回事  -好吧  听着...
- Bob, what's going on? - All right, look...
亲爱的  事实是在那个满是奖杯和灯光的
Honey, the truth is in all the excitement of that night
兴奋之夜里
With the award and the lights--
怎么说呢
I don't know.
我只是  我忘记感谢你
I just-- I forgot to thank you.
然后我们做了这卷带子掩盖这个谎言
And then we made the tape to cover up the lie
我  我真的真的很对不起
And I just-- I'm really really sorry.
听着  鲍伯  我真的  我感谢你的努力
Look, bob, I really-- I appreciate the effort,
但是你为什么得向我撒谎
But why did you have to lie to me?
我是说如果我们之间没有了真诚
I mean if we don't have honesty,
那我们还有什么
What do we have here?
我们这里还有什么
What do we have <i>here?</i>
老妈  根据这张表
Mom, according to your chart,
你的眼睛没有任何问题
It says there's nothing wrong with your eye
你昨天就应该回家了
And you should have gone home yesterday.
嘿  愿意忘掉我们上一分钟所说过的话吗
Hey, you wanna pretend the last minute of our lives never happened?
什么上一分钟
What last minute?
我们两族已经交战多年
Our two peoples have been in conflict for many years.
嗯
Mm.
今天是最后的决战了
Today the final battle begins.
切卡普应该说“接受体罚
Chicapu is supposed to say, "assume the positions
准备高更尼克之战”
And prepare for the gorgonic war."
-查莉  说“开始”  -开始
-Charlie, say "go." -Go!
切卡普已经说了  开始战斗了
Chicapu has spoken. Let the battle commence!
沃达特  快点
Wardart, come quick!
哈  感受下我的愤怒吧  你这无赖
Ha!  Feel my wrath, you knaves!
决不  以高更之名  复仇之魂是我的
Never! Vengeance will be mine in the name of gorgon.
嘿  埃文  埃文  我要怎么做
Hey, Evan, Evan, what am I supposed to do?
-回到现实了  -搞什么飞机
-Reality! -For crying out loud.
你不能用我的人类名字叫我
You can't call me by my human name.
-我是斯莱格沃特  -抱歉  斯莱格沃特
- I'm slegowart. - I'm sorry, slegowart.
又错了  我现在是埃文
No, now I'm evan.
好了  伙计们  我们已经在现实中太久了
Okay, guys, we've been in reality for too long.
游戏开始
Game on!
哦
Ooh!
我受伤了
I am wounded.
切卡普  你真的是个不错的对手
Chicapu, you're a worthy adversary indeed.
快点儿  把你的火球扔出去
Quick, wardart, throw your fireball.
不  别对着我扔  别
No, not at me. No, not--
哈哈  死了  你死了
Ha ha, dead! You are dead.
你到底怎么搞的
What is wrong with you?
是你告诉我扔的
Well, you told me to throw it.
别朝我扔啊  我已经在游戏中被你打死了
Not at me. I'm out of the game now.
难道不能重玩什么的吗
Well, can't you just call backsies or something?
重玩  你多大了  五岁吗
Backsies? What are you, five?
噢  我五岁
Oh, <i>I'm</i> five?
你才是那个围着公园跑
You're the one running around the park
穿得像个大青蛙的人
Dressed like a giant frog.
我是一只魔法蟾蜍
I am a magic toad.
是是  你是
Yes yes, you are,
也就是说我必须现在离开
Which means I must now leave
这片诺丁汉姆的神话大陆了
The mythical land of nerdingham,
因为我已经失去兴趣了
For I have lost interest
不论你穿着泳衣有多好看
No matter how good thou looketh in a swimsuit.
切卡普  咱们走
Chicapu, away!
过来  好的
Come here, you. Okay.
这么说来你把那个女孩带这来约会的
So you brought that girl here on a date?
是的
Yeah.
这几乎就像是我在约会
So it's almost as if I were on a date.
嗨  查莉
Hey, charlie.
听着  等你像我这么大了
Listen, when you get to be my age,
不要为了给一个男孩留下好印象而假装成别人
Don't pretend to be someone you're not just to impress a guy.
我刚刚学到的
I just learned that.
我也学到了如果你穿得像只巨型小鸡
I also learned that if you walk home from the park
从公园走路回家
Dressed like a giant chicken,
你会被狗追的
You're going to be chased by a dog.
你碰我的口袋游戏王牌了吗
Hey, did you touch my pokeo cards?
-没有  -撒谎
-No. -Liar!
我的斯莱格玛牌有一个角被折弯了
There's a bent corner on my slugmar card.
老妈
Mom!
噢  还有一件事
Oh, one more thing.
如果你喜欢上一个和盖比有些像的家伙
If you fall for a guy with something in common with gabe,
那就祝你好运喽  小查莉
Good luck, charlie.
-刘易斯  -你好  邓肯先生
-Lewis! -Hello, mr. D.
进来
Come on in.
嗨  泰迪  刘易斯来了
Hey, teddy, lewis is here.
其实我来是有些话和你说  鲍伯
Actually I came here to talk to you, Bob.
-我可以叫你鲍伯吗  -可以吗
-Can I call you Bob? -Can you?
这将是我的荣幸
It would be my pleasure.
鲍伯  正如你所知道的
Well, Bob, as you know
我和泰迪在一起已经很长时间了
I've been spending a lot of time with Teddy
关系也发展的非常好
And things are going very well.
艾米和我都很高兴
And Amy and I are absolutely thrilled about that.
我的未来很光明啊  先生
My future is bright, sir.
我在漫画书店有一份很好的兼职工作
I have a good part-time job at the comic book store.
-我有自己的自行车  -我想我猜到接下来是什么了
-I own my own bike. -I think I know where this is headed.
我猜我想说的是
I guess what I'm trying to say is...
我请求你允许让泰迪
I'd like your permission to ask Teddy
做我的女朋友
To be my g-girlfriend.
我家欢迎你  好儿子
Welcome to the family, son.
回到现实吧
Reality!
非常感谢你的真人角色扮演  邓肯先生
Well, thank you for the larp, mr. Duncan.
去洗车吧  刘易斯
Just go wash the car, lewis.
遵命  先生
Yes, sir.